A journey of the heart. The adventure of their lives.
Last of the Dogmen is a adventure, mystery,
thriller film directed by Tab Murphy.
A Montana bounty hunter is sent into the wilderness
to track three escaped prisoners.
Instead he sees something that puzzles him.
Later with a female Native Indian history
professor, he returns to find some answers.
Lewis Gates, played by Tom Berenger.
Prof. Lillian Diane Sloan, played by Barbara Hershey.
Sheriff Deegan, played by Kurtwood Smith.
Yellow Wolf, played by Steve Reevis.
Briggs, played by Andrew Miller.
Sears, played by Gregory Scott Cummins.
Last of the Dogmen is a 1995 American Western film written and
directed by Tab Murphy (in his feature directorial debut).
It stars Tom Berenger, Barbara Hershey, Kurtwood Smith and Steve Reevis.
Set in the mountains of northwest Montana, United States, the film is about a bounty hunter who tracks escaped convicts
into a remote region and encounters an unknown band of Dog Soldiers from a tribe of Cheyenne Indians.
The film was shot on location in Alberta and British
Columbia, Canada, as well as in Mexico.
Critical reviews were mixed to positive, though the
film was a box office disappointment.
The film explores themes of bounty hunter, montana,
mountain, forest, anthropologist.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.